techjuice.pk 2017-02-28

# Privacy Policy

We here at TechJuice consider our readers to be of paramount importance. We recognize the need of respecting your privacy, as such we would like to take some time out and tell how we protect your personal information. Rest assured, we will never have the inclination to sell your information to any outside parties.

### **Personal Information acquired by us:**

When you, the user, access our website, we are required to monitor or log several forms of data. These may include but aren’t limited to: IP Address, Your name, ISP, Location, Browser used to open the site, the time you stayed on the site, which articles or pages you opened, and, any other information that we are legally required to obtain. Rest assured, every website in the world does this, some sites will mention this when you open them, others won’t. We have a legal obligation to abide by this regulation. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise release your personal information to outside parties outside of TechJuice.pk.

### **How your cookies help in showing advertisements (for you)**

Techjuice.pk uses third party advertisements to support the company’s monthly costs. These advertisements may use certain technologies such as your cookies, cookies in turn are what gives the advertisement information on what to show you.

These advertising companies may use information (None of which will disclose anything that will identify you; email address or your name) regarding your visiting habits to your browsing history as to be able to give you meaningful advertisements for goods and/or services that could be of interest to you.

If you wish to learn more about how this works, while also making yourself aware about your choices and wish to not have your personal information used by these companies you can email at: fatima[at]techjuice[dot]pk

**If you have any inquiries, questions, or otherwise, you are always welcome to drop us an email on: inbox@techjuice.pk**

* * *
